Art Collins Papers ARC.0001
Library and Archives
Art Collins Papers
Bulk, 1972-2005
1964, 1967-2005, undated
ARC.0001
Library and Archives
38.02 Linear feet (21 records cartons, 3 Hollinger boxes, 2 half Hollinger boxes, 4 audiovisual boxes, 1 audiotape reel, 6 oversize boxes)
Artist manager for Marianne Faithfull and Iggy Pop. Correspondence, fan mail, clippings, song licensing and royalty contracts, tour and album information, photographs, press releases, audio and video associated with Collins' life and work.
Collins, Art, 1953-2005
Separated Materials note
Books, sheet music collections, periodicals, 45 rpm records, DVD-video discs, audiocassettes, VHS videocassettes, single test pressings, and LPs have been transferred to the library collection. Please search for the "Art Collins Papers" in the library catalog for a list of donated titles. If you are unable to find what you are looking for, consult the Library and Archives staff to ensure these materials are available.
Scope and Contents note
The Art Collins Papers span the years 1964 to 2005, with the bulk of the materials dating between 1972 and 2005. The Papers are divided into four series: Iggy Pop, Marianne Faithfull, Personal, and Audiovisual Materials. The bulk of the collection provides rich documentation of Collins’ role as manager to Iggy Pop and Marianne Faithfull. These series consist primarily of song licensing contracts, tour information, album release information, royalty contracts and statements, photographs, and press releases. Additionally, there is material related to Collins' association with the Rolling Stones as vice-president, and then-president of Rolling Stones Records, most notably video footage that can be found in Series IV. Other materials related to Collins personally and to his other clients can be found in Series III, which includes correspondence, fan mail, newspaper and periodical clippings, and audiovisual material. The materials are, for the most part, in their original order as received from donor. Items were only removed from their original order due to size and condition concerns, or if material was obviously misfiled. The Art Collins Papers not only illustrate the impact of Iggy Pop on punk music but also document Marianne Faithfull's reemergence on the music scene. Seen in a more general sense, the Papers provide a behind-the-scenes look at being an artist and manager in the rock music industry as it has evolved over nearly six decades.
Biographical Note
1975 Joins Atlantic Records’ promotion department.
1977 Joins Rolling Stone Records.
1982 Founds Art Collins Management in New York City.
1985 Becomes Iggy Pop’s manager.
1989 Marries Nikki.
2005 July 27 Dies of cardiac arrhythmia.
Art Collins started his career in the music business in 1975, working in the Atlantic Records’ promotion department. He joined Rolling Stones Records in 1977 as the vice president and later became president of the company. In 1982, Collins left Rolling Stone Records and turned his attention to artist management, founding Art Collins Management in New York City. His clients included Joe Jackson, Marianne Faithfull, Marshall Crenshaw, and Iggy Pop, whom Collins managed for over twenty years. Collins died unexpectedly of cardiac arrhythmia at his home in Pine Bush, New York at the age of 52 on July 27, 2005. He was survived by his wife, Nikki, and her sons from a previous marriage, Kieran and Travis McGee.
Sources
Tomcho, Sandy. “Arthur Collins, manager of musicians, dies at 52.” Times Herald Record, July 30, 2005, lasted updated December 17, 2010. Accessed October 31, 2012. http://www.recordonline.com/apps/pbcs.dll/article?AID=/20050730/NEWS/307309992&cid=sitesearch.
“Longtime Iggy Pop Manager Dies Suddenly.” Billboard, July 31, 2005. Accessed October 31, 2012. http://www.iggypop.org/artcollins.html.
Custodial History note
The Art Collins Papers were received by the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame Foundation, Inc. as a gift from Nikki Collins on December 30, 2006. The Rock and Roll Hall of Fame Foundation, Inc. transferred the collection to the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame and Museum, Inc. on March 31, 2011.
Conditions Governing Access note
Collection is open for research. Patrons must sign the Acknowledgment of Legal Responsibility and Privacy Rights section of the Researcher Registration form before using this collection. Some of the materials in the collection are confidential and are, therefore, RESTRICTED. Access copies of these materials may have to be created prior to use. The condition of some of the audiovisual materials in the collection has not yet been determined for playback purposes. Some of the audiovisual materials in the collection are on defunct media formats and, therefore, are RESTRICTED. Access copies of these materials may have to be created prior to use. Consult the Library and Archives staff in advance of your visit to ensure access to these materials is available. Some original materials in the collection are closed. Patrons must use physical facsimiles of original. Use of originals only by permission of the Head Archivist. Some materials are CLOSED until the death of Iggy Pop. Other materials are CLOSED until the death of Nikki Collins. Access to those materials is unavailable until that time. All closed and restricted materials are identified at the folder- or item-level in the Collection Inventory.
Badalamenti, Angelo; Beatles; Collins, Nikki; Faithfull, Marianne; Guns n' Roses (Musical group); Ian, McLagan; Jagger, Mick; Lennon, John, 1940-1980; Pop, Iggy, 1947-; Presley, Elvis, 1935-1977; Richards, Keith, 1943-; Rolling Stones; Stooges (Musical group); 1/4 inch audio tape; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; Accounting; Advertising--Music; Audiocassettes; Betacam SP; Books; CD-Rs; Clippings (Books, newspapers, etc.); Concert tours; Contracts; Copyright--Royalties; Documentary films; Film (material by form); Humanitarianism; Interviews; Lighting--special effects; Mass media and publicity; Music supervision; Music trade--Management; Newspapers; Periodicals; Photographs; Printed ephemera; Punk rock music; Rock music--United States; Rock music--Writing and publishing; Rock videos; Scripts (documents); Set lists; Sheet music; Songs--Texts; Sound recording industry--Management; VHS
- Series I: Iggy Pop [RESTRICTED], 1985-2005, undated
  Scope and Contents note
  Series I: Iggy Pop contains documents pertaining to Iggy Pop’s career, including song licensing, tour information, photographs, merchandising agreements, contracts, professional and personal correspondence, royalty statements, clippings, publications, and press information. The files are arranged as received by the donor. Some material has been stored separately due to size and condition concerns.
  Access Restrictions
  Some of the materials in this series are confidential and are, therefore, RESTRICTED. Access copies of these materials may have to be created prior to use. Some of the materials in this series are CLOSED. In some cases, patrons may be able to use physical facsimiles of the originals. Consult the Library and Archives staff in advance of your visit to ensure access to these materials is available. Restricted materials are identified at the file level, along with their specific restrictions.
  - "Passenger" / Japanese documentary use, 1995-1997 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - No. 1 Drive (CD), "Passenger" / Polygram UK, 1997 June 25 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Maverick Records, Volume 2, "Passenger", 1997 June (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Maverick Records, Volume 3, "Lust" use, 1997 June (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Candy (Bug) radio advertisement / Argentina, 1997 May 28 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Doctor Music Festival letter, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - U.S. Air letter, 1997 June 5 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Freaks of Nature sampler CD, 1997 June 6 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Rynne, Frank, 1996 August 20 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Rutles, 1996 August 20 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - New York Times article, 1996 August 25 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Niagara, Niagara, 1996 August (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Eight Days With Lester, 1996 July 8 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Rock Wives, 1996 July (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Long View Farm Studios, 1996 June 7 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Mesa Boogie Amps, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - BMP (Boase Massimi Pollitt) DDB (Dane Boyle Bernbach) Needham Worldwide, Ltd, 1996 June 18 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Tesco, Nick, 1996 June 12 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - New Yorker Magazine, 1996 April 8 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Virgin Records Canada, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Pulp Magazine, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Skydog Royalties, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Lion's Pride Productions CD, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Wild, Wild Thing, Tank Girl, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Edge-Fest Minnesota, 1996 April 9 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Toronto Road Book, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Sandercock, Carleton, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - "To Belong" video day sheet, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Zermati script, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - I Want My MTV, "Real Wild Child", 1996 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Alexander, Betsy, 1996 March 11 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Esquire request, 1996 February 15 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Flatiron News, 1996 April 12 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Raw Power info, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Live reviews, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Glass Blowers Ball, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Garage Bands, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Road Stories Book, 1996 April 4 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Heckmann, Ulli, photo, 1996 February (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Mac, Jimmy / N. O., 1996 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Mid-price request, 1996 March (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Nagase (Japan), 1996 March 7 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Virgin V.I.P. List, 1996 March 26 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - A&M royalties, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - MTV release - Red Hot Chili Peppers, 1996 February 23 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Rhino Records compilation, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Live 105 Top 105, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - German, Bill, 1996 January (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - "Pussy Walk" sleeve, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Oliveras, Michael resume - bubbles, 1996 January 10 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Nagase / M. Ando, 1996 February 7 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Ardent Studios, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Lucas, Gary, stuff, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Complete Music Services, 1996 January 26 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Slayer / "I Wanna Be Your Dog", 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Joel Reiff Lighting, 1996 January 23 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Wilson, Thom, producer, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Jones, Cliff, book, 1995 April 7 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Atolladero, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Jimi Hendrix Foundation, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Press clips, 1993, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Virgin International Presentation, 1995 July (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Ogilvy and Mather, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Roskilde 25th Anniversary rock film, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Trident Music, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Absolute Vodka, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 66, Box OS1, Folder 1)
  - Rynne, Frank, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA) '95 [RESTRICTED], 1995 February 8 (Box 1, Folder 68)
    Some of the materials in this file are confidential and are, therefore, RESTRICTED. Access copies of these materials may have to be created prior to use. Consult the Library and Archives staff in advance of your visit to ensure access to these materials is available.
  - American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA) Iggy [RESTRICTED], 1995 May 15 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Shure Microphone, Batman Forever contract, 1995 April (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - La La Human Steps, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Pagan Fun Wear (Brian Eno), 1995 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Kozik, Frank (re: Greg Shaw), 1995 (Box 1, Folder 73)
    Related Materials
    Related materials providing content on Greg Shaw and Bomp! Records may be found in the following collections in this repository: ARC-0036 Bomp! Records Collection.
  - Tour managers [RESTRICTED], 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 74)
    General note
    All resumes contained in this folder were destroyed due to privacy concerns.
  - Roadies, 1995, undated (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Musicians, 1995, undated (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Rock, Mick, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Kiss My Blood, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Prince's Trust UK, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - WXRT "1969" CD use, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - "Town Called Malice" "Lust for Life" loop use, 1997 June (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Sagmeister CD covers, 1997 July 4 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - "Lust For Life" Scottish Police use, 1997 May (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - DOD / DigiTech pedals, 1995 February 27 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Joyce Green Hospital, 1994 July 25 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Bug Music Publishing, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 86-88)
  - Siberia release, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 89-90)
  - Point Music (Brian Jones), 1995 December 15 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Elliot, Amy, script, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Shure / Billboard, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Doggie Market, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 94, Folder 47)
  - Edmunds, Ben / Rhino, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Music Express, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Crow [RESTRICTED], 1996 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Boogie Boy, 1996 August 8 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Cufaro, Chris, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Henry, Wendy, contract, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Rock For Choice, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Crow (publicity), 1995 December 20 (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Album Network information, 1995 December (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - "Lust For Life" (DDB Needham), 1995 (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Tour Bus Leasing, circa 1995 (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - O'Brien, Brett (S.O. Pro), 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - Pope, Tim, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - Bomp! Records, 1992-1993, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - Gyson, Brion, Iggy piece, 1995 October 8 (Box 1, Folder 109)
  - Muscle Shoals Studios (Alabama), circa 1996 (Box 1, Folder 110)
  - Sister Midnight, HBO Special Documentary, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 111)
  - Adventures of Pete and Pete contract [RESTRICTED], 1995 November 10 (Box 1, Folder 112)
  - Mike's Artist Management producers, 1995 September 6 (Box 1, Folder 113)
  - Smith, R.J. Halloween pack, 1994 (Box OS1, Folder 1)
  - Barb Wire correspondence, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 114)
  - Vlasic, Marsha, William Morris, 1995 November (Box 1, Folder 115)
  - Details magazine, "Max's Kansas City Special" [photocopy], 1995 November-1995 December (Box 1, Folder 116)
  - Sandra Marsh Management, 1995 December 12 (Box 1, Folder 117)
  - Brown, Julie (M.A.P.), 1995 December 13 (Box 1, Folder 118)
  - "Passenger," Munich Student Film Festival, 1995 October 31 (Box 1, Folder 119)
  - Perri Entertainment (passes, etc.), circa 1996 (Box 1, Folder 120)
  - "Sleeping on the Sun" (presskit), 1995 October 28 (Box 1, Folder 121)
  - Carax, Leos, letter to Iggy, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 122)
  - Virgin International Label Copy, "Heart [is Saved]", 1995 December 13 (Box 1, Folder 123)
  - Ardent Studios (Memphis), 1995 (Box 1, Folder 124)
  - Floating Men Group, 1995 (Box OS1, Folder 1, Box 1, Folder 125)
  - Creative Hands, 1995 December 5 (Box 1, Folder 126)
  - Naughty Little Doggie artwork, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 127)
  - Burns, Andrew, guitar tech, 1995 December 5 (Box 1, Folder 128)
  - Sparks album, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 129)
  - Bosnia thing, 1995 November 20 (Box 1, Folder 130)
    Cradle, aiding the children in Bosnia and Herzegovina.
  - Dresden idea, 1995 November (Box 1, Folder 131)
    Open Air Concert in Dresden, 1996.
  - Cellular One, 1995 November 16 (Box 1, Folder 132)
  - Pop, Iggy and Johnny Depp question and answer [photocopy], 1995 (Box 1, Folder 133)
  - Denius, Wofford ("Ed Hammell"), 1995 September 26 (Box 1, Folder 134)
  - Joint Artists and Musicians Political Action Committee (JAMPAC - Krist Novoselic), 1995 (Box 1, Folder 135)
  - Rock and Roll Hall of Fame, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 136)
  - Potsdam: Berlin, 1994-1996 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Elizabeth Arden, 1995 May 31 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Glasser, Jeanne, 1988-1991, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - New groups, 1995 (Box OS1, Folder 1, Box 2, Folder 4-5)
  - Newsweek / Time Out, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - South By Southwest convention, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Danish compilation, "China Girl", 1996 October (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - APA Drug Awareness UK, 1996 September 19 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Milestones UK, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Swietliki-Fireflies, Polish rock group, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Giddings, John, Summer 1996 dates (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Sidedoor Johnnies, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    This file includes other artists seeking representation.
  - Kenickie Band, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Pine Bush High Scool Parents' Night, 1996 October 3 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Pearl (Warner Brother Television) show, 1996 September 13 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Suddenly Susan license request, 1996 September 13 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Erlich, Dimitri, book request, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Benson, Eric, 1996 September 24 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Matsuda show, 1996 October 16 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Virgin Germany interview disk, 1996 October 17 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Escape From A Wonderful Life, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Anarchy TV (movie), 1996 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Stamaopolous, Dino, 1996 August 7 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Blender Magazine contract, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Music Cares Fund, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - International Peace University, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Copyright renewal (Bug), 1996 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Cold Metal, Italian movie, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Life on Mars CD-ROM Request, 1996 October (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Microsoft CD-ROM request, 1996 October (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - McGroggan, Henry, 1995 March 28 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Bidstrup, Jens, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Sonic Net '95, 1995 July 24 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Naughty Little Doggie reviews, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Arena magazine, circa 1996 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Giddings, John (Ramones), 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Highland Telephone (office), 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 38-39)
  - Europe '96, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Summer 1997 tour dates, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - French tour, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Mexico tour, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Australian tour, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Edgefest, Minneapolis, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Iggy Naughty Little Doggie note, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - U.S. tour '96, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 47-49)
    Files 48-49 contain the front flap of the original folder in order to preserve the writing.
  - "Lust For Life" ( Sunday Times UK), 1997 May 16 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Made in Germany documentary, "The Passenger" use, 1997 June 23 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Hear Records charity CD, 1997 July 27 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Incommunicado Press, book publishers, 1997 June 6 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Resumes, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - DOD Electronics, 1997 June 25 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Platinum use, "Passenger" / "I'm Sick of You", 1997 July 10 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Burt, Bob, baseball collection, 1997 June 18 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Tipton, Michael, 1997 June 25 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Final Rinse script / letter, 1997 June 10 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Farrell, Richard, script letter, circa 1997 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Trainspotting II, 1997 June (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Miller, Stella, Charles Lyonheart, 1997 May 13 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Virgin International updates, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - 1997 International Motion Picture Almanac (Quigley) (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - New album production money, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Mean Fiddler letter, 1996 August 15 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Iggy Japan tour, 1995 November (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Davey, Barry, wire transfer [RESTRICTED], 1996 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Tuborg Beer, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - "Lust For Life" / Brits Awards, 1996 December 11 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Virgin Best of release, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Dole, Bob / Trainspotting, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Ride the Fucking Wild, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Bowie turns 50, 1996 September 15 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Crow / Alain Lahana, 1996 December (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Haust, Jan / Punk Hole of Fame, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Parliament / Funkadelic documentary, 1996 November 21 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Walker, Bob, speakers list, 1996 June 24 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Time Zones / Italy, 1996 December 4 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Terry, Mark, Trainspotting, 1997 March (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - South Bank Show documentaries, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - German Vogue, Uli Heckmann picture, 1997 May 2 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Schermerhorn, Eric, Mesa Boogie Ltd., 1997 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - McGee, David, Iggy letter, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - "Gimme Danger" lead sheet, 1997 February 20 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Milestones (UK) - Brian Eno, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Aitken, Doug, Howard (Shur) / Satellite Films, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Grey, Janet, Personal Hell, 1996 October 10 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Anarchy TV ("I Wanna Live"), 1997 February 6 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - King Biscuit Flower Hour CDs, 1997 February 12 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Pepsi World Website, 1997 March 13 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Eco Quix, R. Grey, 1997 January 27 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Rose, Dan, video, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - "Lust For Life," Trainspotting trailer, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Rock Walk information (L.A.), 1996 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - JSR Merchandising, 1996 May (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Rolling Stone, International Virgin memo, 1996 June 6 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Hard Core Logo, 1996 June 4 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Alex and Levi demos, circa 1996 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Lorre, Inger, demo, 1996 June 5 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Bug Music, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Time Herald Record review, Naughty Little Doggy, 1996 May 17 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - "Real Wild Child," Virgin Best of, 1996 May (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Hustler Magazine, Iggy request, 1996 May 10 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Manzarek, Ray, audio, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - NIL cigarette ad, 1996 May (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Andrew Solt Productions, History of Rock and Roll (and miscellaneous), 1995-1999 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - New groups, 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Federal Express domestic, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Perkins, Carl, obituaries / accounts, 1998 January 20 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Barry, Dave, Mick Jagger article, 1998 January 17 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Virgin Website, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Erlich, Dimitri, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - "Buzzard Song," Porgy and Bess, 1997 September 30 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - January-June 1995 statement, Virgin royalties (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Australia tour, 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 50-51)
  - Rolling Stones MSG tickets, 1998 November (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Pen Pal group, Karen Wilshinsky, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Stisism / Chris Curlyo, circa 1996 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Village Gate, 1994 November 21 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Condoms, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    Regarding HIV infection and other STD prevention.
  - "Porno" / Moby, 1998 March 16 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - 200 Cigarettes, 1998 March 6 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Atlanta date, 1998 February 3 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Germany tour, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Berry, Nancy, Wall Street Journal story, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Italian Vogue wardrobe shoot, 1998 March (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Psycho Backho comic book, 1998 January 20 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Walden Savings Bank [RESTRICTED], 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 63-64)
    Some of the materials in these files are confidential and are, therefore, RESTRICTED. Access copies of these materials may have to be created prior to use. Consult the Library and Archives staff in advance of your visit to ensure access to these materials is available.
  - DeRogatis, Jim, Lester Bangs book, 1997 January 30 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Simpsons, 1997 May 7 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - EMI Music Publishing, 1994-1995, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 67)